You're super late, Marfil.
You can't go a second without me, huh?
- Right.
- You need to be more independent, Tami.
- How's it going?
- Terribly.
Fonteyn is in a particularly
bad mood today.
That's new.
I can't remember the steps.
What do you mean...?
Hey, that was kind of cruel,
don't you think?
No. She can't treat people that way.
- Someone needs to put her in her place.
- Girl.
I'm not talking about Fonteyn.
BASED ON THE BOOK BY
MERCEDES RON
Put her in the van!
DRAWN TOGETHER
Dad?
Marfil.
Dad.
How are you?
Fine. I don't know...
Honey.
You scared me to death.
What happened?
You went missing two days ago.
And last night
someone brought you to the ER.
- What?
- It's okay.
Lay down.
The police were waiting
for you to wake up.
This won't take long, don't worry.
I'm Officer Rivera.
Could you tell us what happened?
Anything you remember.
Yes.
Someone assaulted me from behind.
Did you see the attacker's face?
No. No, I just...
I just remember a voice saying,
"Put her in the van."
Mr. Cortés, did someone contact you
to ask for some kind of ransom?
No.
Well, then this is not a kidnapping.
It's not?
What is it, then?
Look, I have a son in college too.
Sometimes kids lose control,
they drink more than they should,
take something they shouldn't take
and they end up in a bad way.
Logan.
Marfil, you scared the life out of us.
How are you feeling?
Weird. I just want to go home
and get back to normal.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
I changed the lock on the apartment.
What time is the flight?
We only have five minutes.
And you still haven't told her.
Marfil, I need to tell you something
before I go.
You're leaving?
You're not even staying the night?
Listen to me.
I would never leave you alone
after what happened.
So you'll have a bodyguard.
No. No, no way.
No. Dad, no.
You don't realize how serious this is.
It was just a warning.
They wanted to make something clear.
What?
That they can get to you
whenever they want.
Who? Who's "they"?
We don't know yet.
And until we figure it out,
I need to know that there is someone
always with you.
I'm old enough to take care of myself.
This is non-negotiable.
I don't like bodyguards!
I don't like them!
I'm sorry, Logan. I don't.
They remind me that something bad
can happen. I don't want that!
I don't want a repeat
of the Central Park thing.
Marfil.
Something bad has happened.
Until we figure out how to deal with it...
It'll only be temporary.
Until we find out...
Marfil.
He will be your bodyguard.
Sebastian Moore.
Pleased to meet you.
Marfil.
Forgive my daughter.
She has her mother's temper.
- That's all right.
- Sebastian will take care of your safety.
I am asking you, please.
I want your coexistence to be peaceful.
He's going to live with me?
His job is to protect you 24/7.
What about college?
Will he come with me too?
I requested that your lessons be online.
You're asking me to change my whole life.
I can't believe this.
- This is the best option.
- For whom?
- Marfil.
- Is this really necessary?
I'm entrusting you
with my daughter's life.
Don't let me down.
Nothing will happen to her.
It will only be for a while.
Logan.
You're in good hands.
Try to get some sleep.
May I know exactly what orders
my father gave you?
"Orders"?
My duty is to protect you
and to keep Mr. Cortés informed.
I have to put up with you in my own home.
Your father hired me to protect you,
not to listen to your complaints.
No.
He put a watchdog on me
because he doesn't give a shit
who looks after me
as long as he doesn't have to.
Okay.
I guarantee that you won't notice...
I guarantee that I am noticing.
Miss.
Are you going to escort me to my bedroom?
I understand
you don't like this situation.
But it is what it is.
So it'd be best if you got used
to being with me.
It's you who will have to get used
Do you never sleep?
I was about to.
How about a smile?
This guy's so rude.
Marfil.
If we're going to live together,
we should set some rules for...
coexistence.
Because of the towel?
Force of habit.
I was living alone one day ago.
Well, you don't anymore.
How would you feel
if I walked around like that?
Try it one day, we'll see what happens.
GABRIELA - MISSED CALL
Crap.
I need your help.
What is it?
My younger sister,
Gabriela, lives in London.
But I haven't told her
about the kidnapping yet and...
I'm worried something might happen to her.
She's in a boarding school.
She can't get out.
But what if Gabriela gets out and...
I can provide security for your sister.
In fact, I have a colleague in London.
I can call him and ask him.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Ray, did you hear that?
- Loud and clear, buddy.
I need you to contact Wilson.
Wilson? Your friend? The Marine?
Tell him I need his help. He'll agree.
So, you're granting the girl
that concession.
I don't think there's any harm
in granting her one thing.
Hey, the chick at the door,
is she another concession?
- What are you doing? Hey!
- What's going on?
- What's she doing here?
- She's a friend.
I can't go outside, so--
No one can come without asking me.
It could be dangerous.
What's dangerous is me being
in here with you all day.
I swear I'll go crazy
and I'll drive you crazy too.
Sweetie!
- I missed you, bitch.
- Me too! I mean, seriously--
Oh, shit.
Sebastian, my bodyguard.
- Bodyguard?
- I'll explain later.
Miss, I am going to need--
An ID, sure.
I know the protocol.
My dad, you know.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
"Salazar"? Is your father
the Mexican diplomat?
That's right.
Do you need to search my bag?
- That won't be necessary.
- Enough formalities.
This is weird enough as it is.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
If you need me, I'll be in my room.
Is he living with you?
It's my best friend. He's not a threat.
- What's up, beautiful?
- Honey!
- Long time no see.
- I missed you.
- Me too.
- Look... What's up?
We're gonna get wasted!
And who are you?
Wait, so Sebastian
is going to live with you
until they catch whoever kidnapped you?
Yeah.
But it's really weird.
Something doesn't add up.
Why kidnap me for a day and then
release me without asking for ransom?
Just let it go. Look on the bright side.
Now you don't have to go to class.
Look, what happened sucks,
but at least you got something in return.
Can we not joke about this?
- What happened is very serious.
- I wasn't joking.
"In return," huh?
Something must've been given in return.
My dad may not have paid the ransom,
but he must've done something.
It doesn't matter. What matters is
that nothing happened to you.
Come.
Sometimes I remember things.
I was in a dark, cold place.
And there was a narrow mattress.
I felt tired and couldn't see well.
But I could feel someone watching me.
Have you told Sebastian?
No. I don't trust him.
He works for my dad. If he's hiding
something from me, so is Sebastian.
Shouldn't we stay the night?
- I don't want to leave you with him.
- No, that's okay.
- Do you need a ride?
- Since when are you so kind, Liam?
With all this kidnapping stuff,
I'm feeling pretty scared.
That way I won't have to pay for a taxi.
If you need anything, just call me, okay?
I love you, sweetie.
I love you too.
Did you hear that, buddy?
- Did you make sure she's asleep?
- Yes, Ray.
- Are you sure she's asleep?
Did you check for light?
You're a funny guy, aren't you, asshole?
I told you we should've put cameras
in her bedroom.
We are not voyeurs.
I don't like this shit.
So what do I do?
Earn her trust, buddy.
What I'm asking you to do
isn't that difficult.
Okay, then you go. I'll stay here.
Start by being a little less rude
and a little nicer.
Smile.
What's this?
I got up early and made you breakfast.
- Why?
- Why not?
You're acting weird.
Me? I'm just trying to be nice.
That must be it.
So, are you going to eat or...
No. I want to go for a run
before my lessons.
I assume you're coming too.
I'll get changed.
What are you doing? Let's go.
I need some water.
You should change your routine.
It can be dangerous
to always do the same things.
You always come here, right?
After your ballet class.
Have you told my dad?
No.
Why do you hide it from him?
My mother was a ballerina.
When she died,
my dad no longer approved of my dancing.
He didn't want to drive me to class
or come to my recitals.
So, he decided to end it for good
and sent me to boarding school.
I'm sorry.
You should talk to him.
It wouldn't do any good.
Besides, you don't know my dad.
I need you to contact the Russians.
Tell them I want to meet with Kozel.
Alejandro, I understand you're afraid.
I am too.
I have no other choice.
- She was kidnapped because of what I did.
- There were bound to be consequences.
- You put a bomb on his plane.
- It was the perfect opportunity, Logan.
I followed the Russians for months
and I knew all their travel plans.
He was supposed to be on that plane.
With Kozel, nothing is certain.
No one has ever seen him.
His men would rather die than betray him.
Only one thing is certain about him.
That he is dangerous.
And you know that better than anyone.
I didn't start this war.
UNITED KINGDOM
When did Dad tell you?
Yesterday, but I'd rather
you'd told me yourself.
I know, I'm sorry.
I didn't want to worry you. I'm fine.
- And I have a bodyguard now, so...
- Yeah, I know.
Is he hot?
Fuck off, Gabriela.
I'm just curious.
I wanna know if he's hotter than mine.
You're a doofus.
How are things going with him?
Don't give him too much trouble.
No way. He has enough trouble
with my schoolmates.
Who would think of sending a bodyguard
to a girls' boarding school?
I know.
How are you getting along with yours?
He was kind of rude at first,
but he's been nicer lately.
I'm getting used to having him here.
Have you made his life miserable already?
Just enough.
What's that?
I don't know. I'll go see.
I'll talk to you soon. Bye.
Wait, Marfil.
I need to ask you
a very important question.
He's very hot, isn't he?
A little, okay?
I knew it.
All right.
Did you hang a punching bag
without asking me?
I'm sorry.
I can take it down.
- No. That's okay.
- Thanks.
It's hard for me to be
cooped up in here all day.
I need
to let off steam sometimes.
Really?
I'm talking about working out.
So tell me, besides boxing,
is there any other way you let off steam?
I know other techniques.
Can you teach me some?
I don't think that's a good idea.
Why not?
It would be a waste of time.
"A waste of time"?
Are you scared?
Are you scared of me?
Of you?
Tell me.
Don't touch me.
- Are you scared...
- Enough.
- ...I'll beat the hell out of you, soldier?
- Enough, Marfil. Stop.
Answer me.
What lethal technique are you going to use
to defend yourself against me?
- Answer me.
- That's enough.
Do you want me to stop?
Well, then--
Can you do that again?
And I'll leave you alone.
Now you.
Were you expecting me?
Your heels.
Good hearing.
I just remembered I have to go to a party.
- I guess you're coming.
- Doesn't sound like a good idea.
Okay. I'll call
and say we're having it here.
Maybe I won't let them in.
- Good luck with that.
- Okay.
Sebastian, come on.
Just for a little while.
I need to go out and unwind.
Please?
Okay. But only for a couple of hours.
How soon can you be ready?
- I'll wait in the living room.
- And one thing.
I hope it's a quiet party.
You're staying with me.
Marfil.
Can you leave my coat there, please?
Grab me a beer. I'll wait here.
Peekaboo!
- What's up?
- Girl!
You brought Mr. Smiles-A-Lot, huh?
Dude, poor guy. Look at him.
Don't you feel sorry for him?
No. He's having a great time.
Right. Not as much as you teasing him.
You know what they say
about people who quarrel.
They end up hooking up.
Like you two?
You don't offer a ride to a girl
if you're not interested in her.
And I've never seen you
accept a ride from anyone.
- Yeah, you do that.
- Yes.
What do you mean, a drink? Liam.
You don't see him as a playboy
and a party boy anymore?
Yes, I still think
he's a playboy and a party boy,
but, before I realized it,
we clicked and we started dating--
You like him a lot.
- No.
- You like him a lot.
- I don't like him a lot.
- That's crazy.
You goofball.
You're so silly.
Hey, did you say hi to Lisa?
- What?
- Did you say hi to Lisa?
No. Where is she?
She was giving shots
to everyone over there.
Dude, she's hammered.
Let's go get her.
Fucking pig.
- Okay, but what about Liam?
- Wait for me here.
What are you going to do? Sebastian!
I'd rather you yell at me
than not talk to me.
I'm not going to yell at you
for helping your friend.
But in the future,
you should use a hold on someone
only to get out of trouble,
not to get into trouble.
- I didn't know he'd react that way.
- What did you expect?
If I hadn't been there...
That guy was twice your size.
You can't beat him.
You lack the strength and the technique.
What if I had it?
It's not that easy. It's not magic.
So, why don't you teach me more?
Marfil, I taught you one chokehold,
and you saw what happened.
If I'd known how to fight,
I could've helped.
Go ahead, laugh. But how did I do?
You never give up, do you?
You're getting to know me.
Honestly, you were very quick.
And you executed it just as I taught you.
I have a good memory.
Just like elephants.
Okay.
If I train you,
I want something in return.
- I can pay you.
- No.
I want three hours to myself.
Out of this apartment.
While you stay here.
Don't you prefer money?
Okay. Three hours. All right.
We start at 6:00. Tomorrow.
Great.
In the morning.
One minute.
Besides ballet,
have you practiced any other sports?
I can ride a horse.
Contact sports?
Define "contact."
Focus.
You're not making it easy.
What?
Nothing. I said I hope it's easy,
because I'm still half asleep.
Since you're so cocky,
you're bound to face hand-to-hand combat
at some point, like yesterday.
I'll teach you a couple of tricks.
Tricks for hand-to-hand combat?
I know a few tricks too.
You speak Russian?
Of course. My mom was Russian.
Okay.
Since you're small and thin,
your punches need to be very precise
and land in very specific spots
to knock out your opponent ASAP.
Hit and run, like a coward.
No, like a sensible person.
Remember, the key spots are here,
here, here...
and, well, here.
How you strike is very important.
A very quick punch
using all your strength.
One.
Two.
Not bad, but kind of weak.
How long have you been doing ballet?
Since I was little.
Can you kick here?
Okay. How about this high?
- You have great legs.
- Thanks.
Okay. I'm going to teach you
a couple of self-defense techniques.
You know, hit and run.
What if I can't run away?
I don't want you to teach me how to run.
I want to learn how to fight.
Are you okay?
Did I hurt you?
I'm great.
When you fall five times in a row,
you learn how to land.
Try it. Knock me down.
You always remember all the moves.
Just like elephants.
Okay, we're done, aren't we?
Yes, of course.
After ten more minutes
of punching the bag.
Are you serious?
I told you it was hard.
But if you think you can't do it...
"I told you it was hard."
Good morning.
Mr. Cortés is expecting you.
I know.
They agree to a meeting,
but Kozel won't be there.
He has to be there.
After the plane thing...
Offer him the routes.
- I beg your pardon?
- It's the only way to convince him.
- To let him think I'll give them to him.
- What?
If Kozel suspects it's a trap,
he'll kill us all.
Don't forget your place, Logan.
Set up that meeting.
When they see his face, he'll be doomed.
And we'll be safe out of the country.
And bring my daughters.
I want to tell them in person.
I'm taking my three hours.
Fancy a burger
from that place on the corner?
Yeah.
Grab a couple on your way back.
- I'm not going that far.
- Where are you going, then?
See you later, Elephant.
You told me to be nicer.
Yes, to be nicer.
Not to frolic with her on the floor.
She asked me to train her.
It's the best way to keep her at home
while I'm here.
You know, she reminds me of someone.
She's disciplined, but cheeky, stubborn...
You know those people who don't listen?
They never listen.
Does that ring a bell?
Do you think she suspects anything
about her father's business?
No, I don't think so.
Cortés has always kept her away from him.
No wonder,
after what they did to her mother.
Alejandro is pushing for
a face-to-face meeting with Marcus Kozel.
Do you think he'll agree?
Well, I don't know.
You know no one
has ever seen that bastard.
And if anyone saw him,
they didn't live to tell the tale.
I gotta go. Anything else?
Keep your distance with Marfil.
I know how to do my job.
Okay? I'm not a rookie.
Who do you think I am?
That hook... Block. There.
That's better. Easy.
- Hold on. Okay.
- Okay.
LOGAN
Kozel agrees to the meeting.
Sebastian, go and take
a cold shower right now.
Right... But...
That's not keeping your distance.
I don't know what you think
you're seeing there, but--
You're trying to fool me.
Do I look like an idiot?
No more of this training nonsense.
You're going to get into trouble, brother.
You like that girl.
And she likes you.
Don't even think about it. Stop.
In two days, they leave for Spain.
And if all goes well, this will be over.
She'll start a new life,
and you'll move on with yours. Apart.
- Got it?
- Okay. Take it easy, man.
Just because we get along
doesn't mean anything.
I'm not going to screw it up.
Sebastian.
I'll be watching you.
What are you doing up?
My dad wants me to fly to Spain
this weekend. Did you know something?
Only that I have to go with you.
- Where are you going?
- To bed.
When you go out...
do you go visit your family?
A friend?
That's right, go recharge your batteries.
Tomorrow I'm going to beat you up bad.
About that.
There will be no more training.
Why not?
Because I've already
taught you everything I know.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, and you've learned very fast.
I'm actually...
very proud of you.
Good night.
At least give me one last lesson.
As a farewell.
Okay.
But it'll be the last one.
You're up early.
I know, right?
Is there anything
you need to go over or practice?
Tell me what you want.
I want your three hours.
And I'm going to fight for them.
One bout.
And if I win--
It would be a miracle
if you managed to even hit me.
Okay.
If I can hit you once,
you'll spend
your three hours with me today.
And the bodyguard stays here.
Just you and me outside this apartment.
That's a very strange way
to ask me out on a date.
I'm not asking you out.
If I did, you'd say no.
So, I'm going to fight for it.
What's in it for me?
This is getting interesting.
What do you want?
For you to keep your distance.
Okay.
Whenever you're ready, Elephant.
Not so cocky anymore.
I thought you were only going
to use one hand.
Well, I've changed my mind.
Come on.
I won, Sebastian Moore.
Looks like it.
Your three hours are mine.
How long have you been there?
Long enough to notice that's not ballet.
It's very rude to spy on people,
just so you know.
- Let's go. You're in for a long night.
- Okay.
But as soon as we set foot
in the apartment, the date's over.
Sure. Of course.
I'm driving.
Don't even think about it.
I said I wanted to go out with you,
not my bodyguard.
Can't we just walk?
Manhattan isn't that big.
Who said we're staying in Manhattan?
Why are we in Brooklyn?
We're going to eat
the best burgers in New York.
I'm surprised you remembered.
An elephant never forgets.
Never.
How did you know
this is my favorite joint?
I have my secrets too.
Amazing.
What?
Relax. Ketchup doesn't look bad on you.
But I thought you'd be
more into light meals than sandwiches.
There's only one sandwich I like.
Taylor Ham.
A girl like you?
I thought you'd pick something more...
sophisticated.
By "sophisticated,"
you mean "posh," I assume.
- You assume many things.
- You have no idea.
Okay, seriously now.
What would you like to do with your life?
In the future.
Well, I study Economics
because at some point
I will have to work in my dad's company.
My family always had ships, planes.
Later, they built airstrips.
Wherever there's a transport route,
he's behind it.
You're telling me about your father.
But what do you want to do?
What do you really want to do?
I just...
I don't know.
I just know that I want a different life.
But I feel like my dad's always been
setting the course of my life.
He decides where I live,
what I study, what I have to do.
That's why I like to keep ballet a secret.
And I want to make my own decisions.
And to do something worthwhile.
Something that makes my life count.
We have to go.
No, we'll be late. Come on.
- What's the rush? Where are we going?
- Dancing.
Dancing?
I'm kidding. I don't want to lose my toes.
But I know how to dance.
You?
I wish I'd known sooner.
All in good time.
No. It's not possible.
We're going to the movies?
There's a movie I wanna watch with you.
- I'm out of here.
- Yeah, right. No way.
Come here.
Really? Is there nothing else on?
An Officer and a Gentleman,
but I prefer this.
Guess what my favorite scene is.
When Rachel leaves on her private plane
and Frank, from a distance,
can only watch her take off,
but at the last moment, she asks them
to stop the plane to get off,
and he runs into her arms and they kiss
as the most beautiful
love song ever plays.
You're going to get us kicked out.
Okay, but don't act all tough.
- It was funny.
- No.
What do you mean, no?
You're laughing.
I can see you.
- You're laughing.
- Stop.
- You're laughing. I see you. Don't lie.
- Stop it.
What?
We're not in the apartment yet.
We're still on the date.
The date's over.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I can't, I'm sorry.
Just a second ago you could.
Look at me.
Why are you acting like this?
What's wrong?
I'm not acting any particular way.
- Can we talk about what just happened?
- Nothing just happened.
- You just kissed me.
- Enough.
We leave early in the morning.
I'm going to sleep. Okay? Thank you.
Sebastian, stop. Stop, please.
Go to your room.
Only if you come with me.
Why are you so afraid?
I'm not.
I just want you to keep your distance.
I told you.
Okay, I'll go to my room.
But I'm going to leave the door open.
Either you come in or you stay out.
Forever.
SPAIN
- Marfil!
- Honey!
I missed you so much.
- You look so beautiful!
- So do you!
- My girl.
- How are you?
Good. You? Exhausted.
- Hey, is that your bodyguard?
- Yeah, that's him.
Not bad at all.
- What are we doing here, Dad?
- Spending time together.
Isn't that wonderful?
Yeah, but why?
Because I'd like us to say goodbye
to the house where we've been so happy.
You're selling the house?
Girls, what do you think of Buenos Aires?
- Buenos Aires?
- What?
Why not? A change of scenery,
of people, of perspective.
Is this because of the kidnapping?
- This is because I was kidnapped.
- No.
It's because I got a very good offer
for the company.
You're selling the company?
Is that what they asked in return?
You made a deal so they would let me go.
Is that it? Did you make a deal?
Marfil, that's enough!
You don't know what you're talking about.
The last time you sent me abroad was
when Mom died.
And now again.
What's going on, Dad?
I just told you. We're moving.
So, you'd better get used to the idea.
PRIVATE PROPERTY
NO TRESPASSING
Good boy.
Mr. Cortés.
Is everything set for tomorrow?
We've tapped the cameras
at the racetrack.
We'll finally know
what Marcus Kozel looks like.
- We just need him to attend the meeting.
- He'll be there.
I'm offering him my routes.
I'm putting an end to our war.
If you hadn't avenged Natasha's death,
there'd be no war to put an end to.
Natasha's murder, Logan.
Marcus Kozel murdered my wife.
And almost my daughter too.
Marfil was with her?
They cut the brakes on her car
and she crashed into a truck
when she picked up Marfil
from ballet class.
Natasha swerved and took the hit,
and Marfil was unharmed.
Until the kidnapping.
I thought she'd be safe in New York.
Far from the reach of that bastard.
If I had finished him,
he wouldn't have kidnapped Marfil.
And I wouldn't have had to ask
for your help.
I want someone to stay
and keep an eye on my daughters.
Marfil knows I'm hiding something,
and I don't want any surprises.
I'll stay here with them.
The Russians can't suspect a thing.
You have no idea what they're capable of.
My baby.
I just wanted to ride Yaco.
I didn't stray far from the house.
That's not why I'm here.
- Your dad says you're moving to Argentina.
- You wanted distance. There you have it.
When I said that,
I was trying to spare us a problem.
For me, it's not a problem.
Marfil, it's not possible.
Can't you see that?
- Our worlds are very different.
- So what?
Okay, I understand you're upset,
but it's for the best.
One day, you'll understand.
Wow.
That's such a grown-up phrase.
I'd expect that from a brat in my college,
but I thought you were smarter.
At least they'd be able to give you
what you want.
You have no idea what I want.
I know I can't give it to you.
So what does all this mean?
It was just a kiss. Come on.
Really? And why did you kiss me?
I don't know. I wasn't thinking.
- You weren't thinking.
- No.
You're lying.
You let me hit you
so I could get that date.
You're not fooling me.
Don't fool yourself.
Marfil?
Coming! Just a second!
Your father awaits you for dinner.
Sebastian was helping me bring Yaco in.
So you are done, then.
- No. We still have to tidy up and--
- Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
- What will you say to Wilson?
- That you're sleeping
- and you've felt bad since last night.
- Good.
What if he finds out?
Say that I lied to you.
I don't want you to get into trouble.
- Dad has forbidden us to leave the house.
- I don't care.
I need to know what he's hiding from us.
Should we go straight to the box?
- Are you all right?
- It's nothing.
- Yes. I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
My bad. I was distracted
watching the race. I'm sorry.
In that case, good luck with the bets.
I don't bet. I buy horses, actually.
I've got my eye on a few.
I love Cortés' horses.
You're going to buy my father's horses?
- You are Alejandro Cortés' daughter?
- That's right.
Unbelievable.
Well, my name is Iván.
- Marfil.
- It's a pleasure. That's a lovely name.
- Thank you.
- We could discuss it.
The horse thing. If you want.
We could have a drink and talk about it.
- But if you're busy, I won't bother you.
- No.
I wasn't doing anything. Shall we?
All right. Let's go.
- Do you ride?
- Not so much anymore.
They're here.
Cortés.
Kozel. Finally.
Yes.
You made a very good decision.
For you and your family.
For everyone.
Come on.
There he is. Nice to meet you, Mr. Kozel.
It's a shame you have to go.
I was having a great time.
I know. So was I.
We could meet up some other time.
Are you dating anyone?
Are you always this straightforward?
I think that when you want something,
you just have to go for it.
An ambitious belief.
You have to be ambitious
when it's worth it.
No. I'm not dating anyone.
Would you give me your phone number?
The thing is I'm moving to Buenos Aires.
Buenos Aires?
That's the worst excuse I've ever heard.
I've heard some good ones.
- That's the worst one.
- It's not an excuse.
My father is selling the house,
now the horses...
Well, I travel a lot.
I could come visit you.
Of course.
What if I told you
that I already want to see you again?
I'm still here.
And what if I told you
that I've been thinking
about kissing you all this time?
What would you say?
Ray, you got him?
We got him, buddy.
Thanks, man.
It was a pleasure, Marfil.
- Marfil, where are you going?
- I need to be alone.
I'm coming with you.
No, Gabi, you're not coming.
I'd rather you stay here.
What do you mean?
We were going to spend the day together.
I've changed my mind.
- What happened at the racecourse?
- I told you, nothing.
Okay. Sebastian, Marfil is leaving!
Shit.
Come on, come on.
What are you doing?
You can't just walk out
and ditch Wilson like that.
What were you doing at the racecourse?
It was just a kiss.
That's not what I meant.
You think I don't know
you're hiding things from me?
Something's going on
and nobody will tell me.
This is not a game.
You can't just go off on your own.
I'll have to get used to it,
soon I won't have a babysitter anymore.
Besides, what do you care?
I care because
I don't want anything to happen to you.
Are you saying that
as my bodyguard or as Sebastian?
Both. Okay?
Can you slow down, please?
Shit.
- What is it?
- The brakes aren't working.
- What do I do?
- Focus on one point.
- What do I do? Sebastian, what do I do?
- Straighten the wheel.
Keep it that way.
- Two cars coming at us. What do I do?
- On my mark, swerve to the left.
Now!
Shit!
Stay clear!
Watch out! Roadworks ahead!
- What are you going to do?
- Trust me.
Wilson, we were in Alejandro's car.
They were trying to kill him.
You need to leave now.
Yeah, I'm taking Gabriela away.
- Dad.
- Tell me you're all right.
Yes, don't worry.
It was just a little bump.
We're both fine.
Go back to New York. I'll come get you
and we'll leave for Buenos Aires.
I need you to trust me.
I know I owe you a lot of explanations.
I promise I'll tell you everything.
Marfil...
I love you, honey.
NEW YORK
Wilson has brought me to London.
What's going on?
Gabi, I need to ask you a favor.
What?
Stay close to Wilson at all times.
Do not leave the boarding school.
What if the boarding school's
security fails?
- Or Wilson? Then what?
- I'll come to protect you myself.
I'll never let anything happen to you.
Never.
I promise.
Are you okay?
I'll feel better when I take this.
I just wanted to say thank you.
When the accident happened,
you swerved to take the hit.
I did what I had to do.
I don't want anything
to happen to you either.
I've grown fond of you over time.
Even if you don't like it.
Why are you looking at me?
What are you doing?
No.
For fuck's sake.
I do like it.
That you've grown fond of me.
I like you.
I thought you'd be unbearable.
Wow.
Confessing your feelings
isn't your strong suit.
But you're not.
You're beautiful.
Smart.
Brave. Determined and--
We need to get ready.
I don't want to go.
You'll be all right there.
It'll be like starting from scratch.
Sebastian, I can wait for you.
These past few months
I've been so happy with you.
I'm going to miss you very much.
Eventually you will forget everything.
An elephant never forgets.
Logan!
We're leaving, Logan!
Kozel.
I am not Marcus Kozel.
I think you're looking for me.
Hello, Alejandro.
You're probably more used
to doing business with my father.
It's a pity you killed him
by blowing up his plane.
But now I'm in charge.
Rumor has it you tried to trick me.
I don't like being lied to.
I don't know what you've been told,
but it's not true.
I met Marfil.
You have a truly gorgeous daughter.
She's beautiful.
- Are you ready?
- Almost.
What's that?
It was my mother's.
Look.
Sebastian.
No!
- Are you okay? You're hit!
- It's nothing.
- Breathe.
- Okay.
- Go to the door. I'll cover you.
- No, I'm not leaving you alone.
- Are you sure?
- Trust me. I'll be right behind you.
Okay.
- Okay.
- They're coming that way.
- This way.
This way, come on.
What are you doing? Not her! Not her!
We were told that she should be alive.
- Let me go first. They won't shoot me.
- No!
Sebastian!
Get behind me!
No, no way. Are you crazy?
Don't come any closer. I said,
Don't come any closer.
Freeze! Freeze!
- Watch it! Watch it!
- Go! Go!
Stop! Don't move!
Put her in the van!
Come on.
Sebastian, are you okay? Your arm?
It's not serious. Don't worry.
What the fuck are you doing?
- I remember you.
- Marfil.
- "Put her in the van."
That's what you said.
To you, specifically.
You two kidnapped me.
Who are you?
What does the FBI
have to do with all this?
Why did you kidnap me?
- To frighten your dad.
- Why?
We wanted him to ask for our help.
He did and we made a deal.
A deal?
- Information in exchange for protection.
- To protect us from whom?
Your dad's involved in dangerous business.
And he has even worse enemies.
You make him sound like a criminal,
but he's not.
My dad is an honest, hardworking man
who has earned everything he has.
- And you don't know what the fuck you're--
- Your dad did this.
He tried to kill one of his associates,
Marcus Kozel.
He blew up his plane
and still failed to kill him.
But 20 of his men died.
There were going to be consequences,
sooner or later.
All right, we kidnapped you.
But if we hadn't, something much worse
could've happened to you.
Don't, Sebastian.
It's okay. Let her process it.
Where the fuck is Cortés?
She has to leave now!
He'll let us know
when he arrives in New York.
He better hurry up,
because, otherwise, we're fucked.
My dad. He's coming to pick me up.
He sent me a location.
- Where?
- Times Square.
- He wants me to go alone.
- No.
- I don't like it.
- Buddy, think.
If they don't get on that plane
and leave for Buenos Aires,
it could be worse
than what happened tonight.
I don't care what you say, I'm going.
I need to see him.
Okay.
But I'll be following you closely.
And if anything happens, no matter what,
I'm getting you out of there. Understood?
The most important thing is
that you keep your phone close to you.
It's the only way for us to locate you.
It's ready.
It doesn't look like a mic.
That's the idea.
I need a code word.
Something that will let me know
you're in danger.
"Ebony"?
"Ebony And Ivory." The song
by Stevie Wonder and Paul McCartney.
What do you guys listen to? Reggaeton?
For lack of a better one, "ebony."
Okay.
I'll go look for something
I left somewhere around here.
Forgive me.
I couldn't tell you I was an FBI agent.
Marfil,
what we've had
is the only thing that is real
and the only thing
that has made this job worthwhile.
You're telling me this because
we're not going to see each other again.
We're going into witness protection.
That's why we have to leave the country.
If I never see you again,
I want you to know--
No, please. Don't say it.
It's the only thing I want to hear.
If you tell me that, I won't let you go.
Goodbye, Sebastian.
Goodbye, Elephant.
Okay. I'm in position.
Ray.
I got her, buddy.
Ray, talk to me.
Give me a sec, hold on.
Heads up, we've got movement.
- Who is it? Alejandro?
- No.
Marfil!
Logan?
I'm so happy to see you.
Thank goodness you're okay.
Logan? What the hell is he doing here?
I'm going to get her.
Wait, Sebastian.
Give it a minute. See what happens.
Where's my father?
- I'll take you to him now. Shall we?
- Okay.
Go, they're between 44th and 7th.
I see them.
I lost them, Ray.
Ray, where are they?
Where the fuck are they?
Stop, it's not that easy.
Where the fuck are they now?
Fucking hell.
There they are. I've got them.
I'm sending you the location
of Marfil's phone.
There it is.
They're walking into a parking lot
between 43rd and 6th.
Why didn't Dad come get me?
It wouldn't be safe
for Alejandro to be here.
I'll explain everything on the way.
Come on.
You're 100 meters away. Hurry.
I'm tapping into the parking lot cameras.
- Is my dad in there?
- No.
- You were going to take me to him.
- I am. Let's go.
I'm not taking one more step
until you tell me where he is.
I see it. I'm 10 meters away.
Ray, what floor are they on?
- Ray.
- The cameras aren't working. Fuck me.
He had to run away.
What? Why?
Alejandro's businesses
aren't as legal as one might expect.
He had a deal with the FBI,
but they have betrayed us.
Motherfucker. What is he talking about?
I don't like this one bit. Hurry!
If we don't leave here right now,
you may never see him again.
You are in danger too, Marfil.
And there is only one person
who can help us.
Ray, I can't hear you.
Buddy!
Hello, Marfil.
Iván?
Who the hell is Iván?
He's the one who's going to help us.
Get in, please.
Ray, it's a trap.
What is this?
Do you know where my father is?
All in due time.
Logan, what is going on?
Logan!
Marfil, may I?
Let's go.
Got anything to say?
Ebony.
THE STORY CONTINUES IN
DRAWN APART